# Jeanne Locker

Motivated, adaptable computer science (and political science!) graduate of Barnard College with varied software development internship experience. Experienced in full project life cycle, from design to integration with extensive collaboration with developers and designers. Excellent at problem solving and learning on the fly.

150 W 87th St. New York, NY 10024 (917) 692-8407 jealocker@gmail.com https://github.com/jlox

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Barnard College** — Programming Consultant

JUNE - AUGUST 2020

• Taught Speech Perception Lab members basic Python and programming skills to build tools related to their research.

## **Major League Baseball** — Software Engineering Intern

MAY 2019 - AUGUST 2019

- Collaborated with software engineers using various technologies, including React, to develop, repair, and refactor code for increased performance.
- Utilized geographic information systems for a client-facing mobile application created for the 2019 All Star Game.

## **Marketing Evolution** — Software Development Intern

JUNE 2018 - AUGUST 2018

- Attended development team training, daily meetings and huddles.
- Wrote clean, clear, and well-tested code for a fully automated data aggregation tool to be used in company machine learning models.
- Used various AWS tools, and attended the 2018 AWS Summit

## **Codespeak Labs** — Teaching Assistant

**DECEMBER 2016 - JUNE 2018** 

- Taught first through eighth grade students basic computer science principles using code.org and similar tools.
- Partnered with supervisors and school teachers to plan and implement lessons following Codespeak Labs' curriculum.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Barnard College of Columbia University**, New York — BA

AUGUST 2016 - MAY 2020

- Technical Editor of Bwog.com, a student news organization, 2019–2020.
- Coursework in computer science fundamentals, artificial intelligence, computer vision and graphics, as well as American politics and political theory.

## Stuyvesant High School, New York

SEPTEMBER 2012 - IUNE 2016

### **SKILLS**

C, Java, Javascript, Python, React.js, Git

Basic Swift, Scala

Knowledge of AWS, SQL

Creative thinking, problem solving, multitasking

Can type over 100 WPM

#### **AWARDS**

Dean's List Fall 2016, Fall 2018, Spring 2019

#### **LANGUAGES**

English, Native Speaker

Korean, Beginner